{
    "id": "5045e09eaaf9480e9c1f9167bea3d470",
    "title": "To, With And By",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Be patient …………………… .. children.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7e1564dd3212447f99f739019c701065"
        },
        {
            "question": "I parted ………………… her after many years of courtship.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "from",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c69edbeb1c834294bd6ba4d95924fe2c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Oil does not mix ..................................... water.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b79e9a2ef1784326a11268afe4ad8b0c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Are you ....................................... me or against me in this matter?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dc7426fb7cf6488d99081b05af86f31e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let me know ........................................ tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "within",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "98bfcea4fc3e4590a1054e76a73ca362"
        },
        {
            "question": "Somebody has just gone ...................................... the window.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "by",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "13c85ec8364a46ce966f04c3d8645cfd"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is two o’clock ......................................... my watch.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "by",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b647c8870b464320832cc386e0102a8b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our team won the match ..................................... six goals to three.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4ebf96af5f0c4cee8fded9d19c388416"
        },
        {
            "question": "We stayed .......................................... the end of the play.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6f5500bd1e634e289eab0270f7188e4a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I prefer walking ........................................ climbing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "72f2d2dd66194a548f9e359d6e91ff0a"
        }
    ]
}